Rockville Journal World War II Letters
Vernon Historical Society
- Inventory
  - Pollansky, Andrew, undated; Narsarssuak; Greenland; Assigned in Greenland; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Pollio, Seraphen, undated; Camp Edwards; MA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Pollio, Seraphen, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Popick, James, undated; Canada; with Enclosure; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Popick, James, undated; Canada; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Popick, James, undated; Minneapolis; MN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Popick, James, undated; Fort St John; Canada; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Popick, James, undated; Canada; with Photos; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Popick, James, undated; Seattle,WA; Scenery; Haines,AK; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Poreda, Edward H, undated; Airborne Eng Aviation Bat; France; Serving as Truck Operator; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Porter, John H, undated; Pearl Harbor; HI; Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prachniak, Stanley, undated; Luzon; Philippines; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prachniak, Stanley, undated; Luzon; Philippines; Bronze Star Awarded; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prachniak, Stanley, undated; Luzon; Philippines; Returning and Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prachniak, Stanley, undated; Luzon; Philippines; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prachniak, Stanley, undated; Luzon; Philippines; 4th Year Overseas, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Pratt, John L, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Pratt, Robert J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Pratt, Robert J, undated; Mrs W J Pratt; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Pratt, James R, undated; Greensboro; NC; Reassignment; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Pratt, Robert J, undated; Pearl Harbor; HI; Returning Home; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Pratt, Robert J, undated; Leyte; Philippines; Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prentiss, Elmer W, undated; Mrs Elmer W Prentiss; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prentiss, Elmer W, undated; Mrs Elmer W Prentiss; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Preuss, Norman J, undated; Juneau; AK; with Newspaper Enclosure; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prokop, Paul H, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 14 Oak Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prucha, William F, undated; England; Military Service; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prucha, Emil J, undated; Italy; History of Aviation Engineer Battalion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prutting, William C, undated; Miami Beach, FL; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prutting, William C, undated; Miami Beach, FL; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Prutting, William C, undated; Miami Beach; FL; Part of a Recruting Team; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Purnell, Kerwin F, undated; Bedford,PA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Purnell, Kerwin F, undated; Sampson,NY; Scenery; Seneca Lake, Geneva, NY; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Purnell, Kerwin F, undated; Sampson NY; Completed Training; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Purnell, Nelson K, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 86 Grand Avenue; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Purnell, Ernest S, undated; Kessler Field; Biloxi, MS; Starting Air Force Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Purnell, Nelson K, undated; Truax Field; Madison, WI; Enrolled in Radio Mechanics School; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Putz, Joseph C, undated; Kelly Field; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Putz, Leopold F, undated; Corpus Christi; TX; with Photo; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Putz, Leopold F, undated; Corpus Christi; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Putz, Leopold F, undated; Corpus Christi; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Putz, Leopold F, undated; Brooklyn; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Putz, Leopold F, undated; Corpus Christi; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Putz, Leopold F, undated; Corpus Christi; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Putz, Leopold F, undated; Cabaniss Field,TX; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Putz, Leopold F, undated; Tolland Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Raczkowski, Henry J, undated; Fort McClellan; AL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Raczkowski, Henry J, undated; Aberdeen Proving Ground; MD; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Raczkowski, Henry J, undated; Aberdeen Proving Ground; MD; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Raczkowski, Henry J, undated; Camp Gordon; PA; Marksmanship Award; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ramsey, Laurence, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Randall, Bradford, undated; Pesacola,FL; Air Force; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rankin, Walter J, undated; Gulf Port; MS; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rankin, Robert W, undated; Fort Adams; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rankin, Robert W, undated; APO 713; San Francisco, CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rankin, Robert W, undated; New Guinea; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rankin, Robert W, undated; APO 713; San Francisco, CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rankin, Robert W, undated; New Guinea; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rankin, Robert W, undated; APO San Francisco; with Paper "Guinea Gold"; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rankin, Walter J, undated; Promotion, New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rankin, Robert W, undated; New Guinea; Completed 20 Months Service,Military Rec; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rau, Frank W Jr, undated; Elgin Field; FL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rau, Frank W Jr, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 6 Church Street; Son of Mr and Mrs Frank Rau; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rau, Norman W, undated; Italy; Served in Eng Unit w/ Other Rockville Men; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rawlings, John, undated; Formerly of Rockville; Killed in Action; From Appleton Wisconsin; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ray, Andrew, undated; New Guinea; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ray, Frederick, undated; Greensboro; NC; At Basic Training for Army Air Force; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Read, Truman W, undated; Esler Field; LA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Regan, Herbert James, undated; NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Regan, Herbert James, undated; USS Altair; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Regan, Herbert James, undated; Pier 92; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Regan, Joseph F, undated; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Regan, Herbert James, undated; Newport, RI; Camp Life; Naval Training Station; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Regan, Herbert James, undated; Boston,MA; City Life; Hotel Somerset; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Regan, Herbert James, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Regan, Joseph F, undated; Tolland Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Regan, Joseph F, undated; Mrs Regan; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Regan, Joseph F, undated; Mrs William Regan; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Regan, Joseph F, undated; Frederick Army Air Field; OK; Finished Flight Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Reiske, William, undated; Marianas Islands; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Remkiewicz, Frank J, undated; El Toro; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Remkiewicz, Frank J, undated; Camp Pendleton; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Remkiewicz, Frank J, undated; Miramar; San Diego CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Remkiewicz, Jerome S, undated; Corpus Christi; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Remkiewicz, Frank J, undated; San Diego,CA; City Life; Old Mission Guadalupe Church, Juarez, Mex; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Remkiewicz, Jerome S, undated; Corpus Christi,TX; Scenery; Pan-Amer Highway,Laredo,TX to Mex City; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Remkiewicz, Mitchell J, undated; Mrs H Remkiewicz; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Remkiewicz, Raymond H, undated; Bergan; Norway; Sailed to Norway; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Reudgen, William F, undated; Sheppard Field; TX; Finished Mechanics Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Reynolds, Robert Lewis, undated; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Reynolds, Robert Lewis, undated; British Solomon Islands; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Reynolds, Robert Lewis, undated; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Reynolds, Robert Lewis, undated; FPO San Francisco; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Reynolds, Robert Lewis, undated; Bainbridge,MD; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Reynolds, Maurice R, undated; 15th AAF; Italy; Serving as a Gunner on a Bomber; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rich, Earl, undated; Cherry Point; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rich, Earl, undated; Edenton; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rich, Joe, undated; Bermuda; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rich, Madeline, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rich, Earl, undated; Cherry Point,NC; USMC; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rich, Earl, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; RFD #2; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rich, Madeline, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Richard, John Jr, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Richard, John Jr, undated; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Richard, Clifford, undated; Camp Wheeler; GA; Has Enlisted; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rick, Gerard J, undated; Hawaiian Islands; See Rock, Gerald; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ridzon, Julia, undated; Madigan General Hospital; Fort Lewis, WA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ridzon, Julia, undated; Baxter General Hospital; Spokane, WA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ridzon, Julia, undated; Madigan General Hospital; Tacoma, WA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ridzon, Julia, undated; Camp Stoneman; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ridzon, Julia, undated; Spokane; WA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ridzon, Julia, undated; El Paso; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ridzon, Julia, undated; Dibble General Hospital; Menlo Park, CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ridzon, Susan, undated; Helen Ridzon; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ridzon, Julia, undated; El Paso; TX; Graduated from Medical Tech Program; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ridzon, Julia, undated; El Paso; TX; Graduated from Medical Tech Program; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Risley, George, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rizy, William A, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; RFD #1; Aviation Cadet USNR; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rizy, Francis K, undated; Tokyo; Japan; Serving on a Cruiser; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rizy, Francis K, undated; USS Oakland; Pacific; Serving on a Cruiser; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rizy, William A, undated; New York; NY; Reported for Flight School; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rizy, William A, undated; USS Hoggatt Bay; Military Service; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Robidas, Roland A, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Prospect Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Robinson, Charles, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rock, Gerald J, undated; Hawaii; with Honolulu Newspaper Page; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rock, Gerald J, undated; Guam; with Enclosure Newspaper; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Roman, J T, undated; Camp Blanding; FL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Romano, Joseph, undated; 15th AAF; Italy; Awarded Unit Badge; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Romeo, John, undated; USS Dayton; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Romeo, John, undated; USS Alabama; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Romeo, John, undated; Shoemaker,CA; City Life; Chinatown,San Francisco,CA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ronalter, Donald E, undated; 5th Army; Italy; History of 363rd Infantry; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Oahu; Hawaii; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Osaka; Japan; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Osaka; Japan; with Enc, Japan Flag Fabric/Newsp Japan,Mil; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Japan; City Life; Iisaka,Japan, Hot Springs; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Japan; City Life; Japanese Temple,Osaka; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Osaka,Japan; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Camp Breckinridge, KY; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Camp Breckinridge, KY; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Camp Rucker,AL; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Hawaii; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Camp Rucker,AL; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Oahu,HI; Scenery; Waikiki Beach and Diamond Head; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Hawaii; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Nashville,TN; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rosenberg, Alfred J, undated; Oahu,HI; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Roszczewski, Edward, undated; Lincoln; NE; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rounds, John C, undated; New York City; NY; Serving on Destroyer; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Rowe, Leon L., undated; Staff Sargeant; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Roy, Raymond R, undated; USS Corbesier; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Roy, Raymond R, undated; USS Corbesier; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Roy, Raymond R, undated; USS Corbesier; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Roy, Raymond R, undated; USS Corbesier; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Roy, Raymond R, undated; Sampson,NY; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Roy, Raymond R, undated; Sampson NY; Completed Training; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Roy, Raymond R, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 76 Brooklyn Street; Son of Mrs Florence Roy; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ryan, LeRoy G, undated; Navy Pier; Chicago, IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ryan, LeRoy G, undated; Pesacola,FL; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ryan, LeRoy G, undated; Sampson,NY; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Ryan, LeRoy G, undated; Sampson NY; Completed Training; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Washington; DC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Washington; DC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Washington; DC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Cambridge; MA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Cambridge; MA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Brooklyn; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Philippines; FPO San Francisco; Encl:Page w/Phil Stamps,Chaplin Message; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Philippines; Enclosures:2 Newspapers, Clippings; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; San Francisco; Enclosure:Press Release; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Shanghai; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Shanghai; Enclosure:Newspaper From Shanghai; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Francis, undated; Camp Swift,TX; Texas; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Francis X, undated; Camp Butner; NC; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Francis X, undated; Fort Polk; LA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Francis X, undated; England; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Francis X, undated; Camp Polk; LA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Francis X, undated; Camp Butner; NC; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Francis X, undated; Bavaria; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Francis X, undated; Fort Bliss; TX; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Francis X, undated; Germany; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Japan; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Salt Lake City, UT; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Fort Schuyler; Navy; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Fort Schuyler; Navy; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Cambridge,MA; Navy; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Panama Canal; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Japan; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Salt Lake City, UT; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Fort Schuyler; Navy; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Fort Schuyler; Navy; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Cambridge,MA; Navy; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Panama Canal; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Maximilian, undated; Fresno; CA; Interviewed Soldier; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Maximilian, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Antoni, undated; William V Sadlak; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Francis X, undated; William V Sadlak; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sadlak, Maximilian, undated; William V Sadlak; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Saidak, Louis T, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; 113 Brooklyn Street; Mrs Louis T Saidak; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Saidak, Louis T, undated; Camp Gordon; GA; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Sas, Chester, undated; Camp Lee; VA; Completed Officer's Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Satryb, William T, undated; European Theater; Artilleryman Training for Europe Invasion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Saunders, Lester C, undated; 5th Army; Italy; Received Combat Award; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Savitski, Serge P, undated; Italy; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Savitski, Serge P, undated; Italy; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Savitski, Serge P, undated; Italy; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Savitski, Serge P, undated; Miami; FL; Returning Home, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Burton, undated; Uvalde; TX; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Burton, undated; Burma; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Burton, undated; San Antonio; TX; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Burton, undated; San Antonio; TX; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Burton, undated; Kent; OH; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Burton, undated; Malden; MO; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Burton, undated; Greensboro; NC; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Earl R, undated; Sampson; NY; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Earl R, undated; Green Cove Springs; FL; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Burton, undated; Change of Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Earl R, undated; Left for Service in the Navy; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaefer, Burton, undated; San Antonio; TX; Attending Flight School; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaeffer, Charles W, undated; Mrs Charles Schaffer; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schaeffer, Charles W, undated; Italy; Promoted; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Scheuy, Allen E, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Scheuy, Norman B, undated; South Pacific; Promoted; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schindler, Earl J, undated; Truar Field,WI; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schindler, Earl J, undated; Selfridge Field; MI; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schindler, Earl J, undated; Northern Solomons; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schindler, Earl J, undated; Okizake; Japan; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schmalz, Arthur H, undated; West Springfield; MA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, Norman R, undated; Fort Dix,NJ; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, Norman R, undated; Fort Dix,NJ; Camp Life; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, Norman R, undated; Camp Grant,IL; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, Norman R, undated; Atlantic City,NJ; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, Elmer W, undated; Fort Bliss; TX; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, Elmer W, undated; Fort Bliss; TX; Mentioned in Letter From Joseph Deslauris; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, Norman R, undated; Paris; France; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Schneider, Norman R, undated; Atlantic City; NJ; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)